(Penny:)...because it would be floating
in a weightless environment.
(Penny:)Yeah, that's right,
the slow reader used science. Suck on that.
- Was there anything valuable in the car?
- Our clothes, our wallets, phones.
And about $300 worth of makeup...
(Raj:)...so this thief could look like
anyone right now.
(Policeman:)Makeup? Sure.
(Leonard:)We're going to the Comic-Con in Bakersfield.
They have a big costume contest.
(Leonard:)It's cooler than it sounds.
(Policeman:)I don't know, sounds pretty cool.
(Raj:)It is. It's not just comic books.
(Raj:)They've got action figures,
toys, a Tron themed dance party...
(Leonard:)Okay, he gets how cool it is.
(Policeman:)I think I have all I need here.
You guys need me to call someone?
(Policeman:)I'm guessing your moms?
(Leonard:)Thanks, but we've got it covered.
(Howard:)Okay, I just talked to my mom.